affiliatefirst.com 2004-06-10

# AffiliateFirst Submission Services

AffiliateFirst has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [AffiliateFirst.com](http://www.affiliatefirst.com/)

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and is only used by AffiliateFirst.  

#### Advertisers

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we currently do use cookies to save login information, we do not extract any information from your computer, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

#### Registration Forms (Merchants)

Our site's registration form request merchants to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), and demographic information (like their zip code).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to send information about our company, and to get in touch with the merchant when necessary. This information is never shared with any outside company or individual.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to send postal mail when necessary.

Merchant information is never used for promotional purposes other than to request additional information for listings on AffiliateFirst.

Mailing List/Opt In

Currently the only only information we need is a name and email address. You can opt out of this mailing list at anytime.

Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests.  Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).  Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.  Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

#### External Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that AffiliateFirst is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us .

  1. You can visit the following URL: [http://www.affiliatefirst.com](http://www.affiliatefirst.com/cgi-bin/page.cgi?p=contact&d=1)

#### Data Quality/Access

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

  1. You can [contact us](http://www.affiliatefirst.com/cgi-bin/page.cgi?p=contact&d=1)

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site  

or by mail; AffiliateFirst  241 W. 97th St.,14K, New York, NY, 10025 **   ******
